the unlike music world is going crazy
because alt Rock squint God's radio head
of one of my and Scott ochman's favorite
bands I might add
Scott together several times uh there
there might release an album Scott
everything then you knew we were going
to talk about it here on television okay
okay okay okay there's a lot of Clues
there's a lot of Clues first up fans
were mail postcards that read burn the
witch and then radio had began deleting
their entire interet social media
presence uh doing this
there it
[Laughter]
goes who knows who knows why are they
Vanishing why are they
Vanishing either either there's a new
radio head Alum Toms just in one of his
moods
uh or maybe lp9 is finally on the way so
uh comedians since all we can do is
theorize right now what do you think is
going on Rachel I think they're really
upset that Miley stopped following them
on Twitter
point I think so
yeah very
upset Scott I think radio head is being
erased like in Back to the Future
because Tom York couldn't trick his
parents intoing yeah
point
right if they don't dance they can't
fall in love if they don't fall in love
they can't kiss and then I'm history
let's play a radio song at the prom
everyone
scatters
hey Tom York you know that new sound
you've been looking
for well listen to
this Karma Police they're really
funny keep going Karma Police at the
under the sea Dance and makes it a much
different movie weird out uh they're
forsaking the internet and releasing
their next album exclusively on handmade
musical dreamcatchers yes fun fun that
could that could be very
true
we're releasing our next album on spider
web a spider will come and spin a web in
your home and pluck the
strings uh Please Release another album
radio head and then I I want to meet
you